Finding Aid for James B. Griffin Papers 1922-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- North American Archaeology Card Files, circa 1930s-1990s; 122 linear feet
  - Geographic Areas and Cultures
    - Central Mississippi Valley Archaeological Survey
      - Site Cards
        - 21-N-4, Lake Mabin (Box 126)
        - Duplicate Cards (Box 126)
    - Pottery Types
      - General (Box 127)
      - Mississippi Sites, L.S.U. Collection (Box 127)
      - Arkansas
        - Zoomorphic Head, Curled Tail (Box 127)
        - Fingernail Punctated Jars (Box 127)
        - Multiple Handled Jars (Box 127)
        - Vertically Ridged Jars (Box 127)
        - Fish Effigy Bowls (Box 127)
        - Mississippi
          - St. Francis Plain (Box 127)
          - Pans (Box 127)
          - Bowls (Box 127)
          - Plates (Box 127)
          - Jars (Box 127)
          - Bottles (Box 127)
          - Loop Handles (Box 127)
          - Strap Handles (Box 127)
          - Arcaded Rims (Box 127)
          - Lug Handles (Box 127)
          - Ribbed Rims (Box 127)
          - Notched Lips and Rims (Box 127)
          - Parkin Punctated (Box 127)
          - Barton Incised (Box 127)
          - Turnbow Punctate Incised (Box 127)
          - Ranch Incised (Box 127)
          - Castile Linear Punctated (Box 127)
          - Tyronza Punctated (Box 127)
          - Fortune Noded (Box 127)
          - Pouncey Pinched (Box 127)
          - Manley Puntated (Box 127)
          - Kent Incised (Box 127)
          - Vernon Paul Applique (Box 127)
          - Rhodes Incised (Box 127)
          - Wallace Incised (Box 127)
          - Owens Punctated (Box 127)
          - Bell Plain (Box 127)
          - Nickel Plain (Box 127)
          - Bell Plain (Box 127)
          - Hull Engraved (Box 127)
          - Walls Engraved (Box 127)
          - Turnbow Incised (Box 127)
          - Rose Red (Box 127)
          - St. Francis Polychrome (Box 127)
          - Hollywood Red-On-Buff (Box 127)
        - Woodland
          - Clay Tempered, Minor Types (Box 127)
          - Baytown Plain (Box 127)
          - Mulberry Creek Cord Marked (Box 127)
          - Wheeler Check Stamp (Box 127)
          - Nickle Cord Marked (Box 127)
          - Fabric Impressed (Box 127)
          - Bowie Plain (Box 127)
          - Larto Red Filmed (Box 127)
    - Louisiana
      - General (Box 128)
      - Louisiana Pottery Types (Box 128)
      - Tchefuncte
        - Tchefuncte Plain (Box 128)
        - Tchefuncte Incised (Box 128)
        - Tchefuncte Stamped (Box 128)
        - O'Neal Plain (Box 128)
        - Alexander Incised (Box 128)
        - Alexander Pinched (Box 128)
        - Lake Borgne Incised (Box 128)
        - LaSalle Punctated (Box 128)
      - Marksville
        - Marksville Plain (Box 128)
        - Marksville Period Rim (Box 128)
        - Marksville Incised (Box 128)
        - Marksville Stamped (Box 128)
      - Troyville
        - Troyville Plain (Box 128)
        - Troyville Stamped (Box 128)
        - Yokena Incised (Box 128)
        - Churupa Punctated (Box 128)
        - Larto Red Filmed (Box 128)
        - Woodville Red Filmed (Box 128)
        - Deasonville Cord Marked (Box 128)
      - Coles Creek
        - Coles Creek Plain (Box 128)
        - Coles Creek Incised (Box 128)
        - French Fork Incised (Box 128)
        - Rhinehardt Punctated (Box 128)
        - Chevalier Stamped (Box 128)
        - Chase Incised (Box 128)
        - Coles Creek Pinched (Box 128)
        - Beldeau Incised (Box 128)
        - Mazique Incised (Box 128)
        - Pontchartrain Check Stamped (Box 128)
      - Plaquemine (Box 128)
      - Natchezan (Box 128)
      - Delta (Box 128)
      - Tchefuncte
        - Tchefuncte (Box 128)
        - Big Oak Island (Box 128)
        - Little Woods (Box 128)
        - Copell (Box 128)
        - Lafayette (Box 128)
        - Lake Louie (Box 128)
        - Poverty Point (Box 128)
        - Motley Place (Box 128)
      - Marksville
        - Marksville (Box 128)
        - Crooks, La-3 (Box 129)
        - Briar Bend Landing (Box 129)
        - Mansura, Av25 (Box 129)
        - Saline Point (Box 129)
        - Veazey (Box 129)
        - Mayer Place (Box 129)
      - Troyville
        - Peck (Box 129)
        - Troyville (Box 129)
        - Greenhouse (Box 129)
      - Coles Creek
        - Caddo (Box 129)
        - Morgan (Box 129)
        - Myatt's Landing (Box 129)
      - Plaquemine
        - Plaquemine (Box 129)
        - Sanson Place (Box 129)
        - Sycamore Landing (Box 129)
        - Turkey Point Landing (Box 129)
        - Mayes Mound (Box 129)
        - L'Eau Noire Bayou (Box 129)
        - Johnson Place (Box 129)
        - Laborde (Box 129)
      - Natchezan
        - Canebrake (Box 129)
        - Ward Place (Box 129)
        - Seven Pines Landing (Box 129)
      - Caddoan (Box 129)
      - Glendora
        - Glendora (Box 129)
        - Keno Place (Box 129)
        - Bray Landing (Box 129)
        - Gahagan (Box 129)
        - Glendale (Box 129)
        - Lakeplace (Box 129)
        - Belcher (Box 129)
    - Mississippi
      - General (Box 130)
      - Clear Creek, 22La542 (Box 130)
      - McRae (Box 130)
      - Miller (Box 130)
      - Anderson Landing (Box 130)
      - White (Box 130)
      - Lake George (Box 130)
      - Shadyside Landinf (Box 130)
      - Mississippi (Box 130)
      - Glass-Natchez
        - Selzertown (Box 130)
        - Anna (Box 130)
        - Neblett Landing (Box 130)
        - Glass (Box 130)
        - Ratcliffe (Box 130)
        - Fatherland (Box 130)
        - Harris (Box 130)
      - Big Black
        - Dupree (Box 130)
        - Chickasaw Old Fields (Box 130)
    - Missouri Survey
      - Monks Mound (Box 131)
      - Pike (Box 131)
      - Lincoln (Box 131)
      - St. Charles (Box 131)
      - St. Louis
        - Big Mound, St. Louis (Box 131)
      - Jefferson
        - St. Joseph (Box 131)
        - Boyce (Box 131)
        - Long (Box 131)
        - Schock (Box 131)
        - Govro (Box 131)
        - Jenni (Box 131)
        - Herrell, J55 (Box 131)
        - Pittsburg (Box 131)
        - McCormack (Box 131)
        - Hidden Valley (Box 131)
        - Lambert (Box 131)
        - Rouggly (Box 131)
        - Bonacker (Box 131)
    - Missouri
      - General (Box 132)
      - Jokehurst Collection (Box 132)
      - Graham Cave (Box 132)
      - Turner, JA-35 (Box 132)
      - Woodland (Box 132)
      - Folsom, Montgomery Co. (Box 132)
      - Aring-Pearl (Box 132)
      - Mississippi
        - Steele Collection (Box 132)
      - New Madrid (Box 132)
      - Scott
      - Stoddard (Box 132)
      - Pemiscot
        - Reynolds Collection (Box 133)
      - Dunklin (Box 133)
      - Morgan (Box 133)
      - Ste. Genevieve (Box 133)
      - Perry (Box 133)
      - Wayne (Box 133)
      - Butler
        - Mississippi (Box 133)
        - Middle Mississippi (Box 133)
      - New Madrid
        - New Madrid County (Box 133)
        - Matthews, NM3 (Box 133)
        - Lewis' Prairie (Box 133)
        - Swallow (Box 133)
      - Scott County (Box 134)
      - Benton County (Box 134)
      - Stoddard County (Box 134)
      - Phelps County (Box 134)
      - Pemiscott County (Box 134)
    - Missouri Cultures
      - Potter and Engleman Sites (Box 134)
      - Other Sites
        - Steed-Kisker (Box 135)
        - Upper Mississippi (Box 135)
        - Oneota (Box 135)
        - Utz Component (Box 135)
    - Arkansas Pottery
      - General (Box 136)
      - Arkansas (Box 136)
      - Arkansas Post (Box 136)
      - Pecan Pt. (Box 136)
      - Knapp Site (Box 136)
      - Tillar (Box 136)
      - U. Chicago Arkansas Pictorial Survey Duplicates (Box 136)
      - Miscellaneous (incomplete information) (Box 137)
      - Possible DeSoto Sites (multiple states) (Box 137)
      - Eastern U.S. Painted Pottery (Box 137)
      - General (Box 138)
      - Arkansas County (Box 138)
      - Crittenden (Box 138)
      - Phillips County
        - U. of Arkansas Collection (Box 138)
      - St. Francis River (Box 138)
      - Monette (Box 138)
      - Earle (Box 139)
      - Neely's Ferry (Box 139)
      - Cherry Valley (Box 139)
      - Pecan Point (Box 139)
      - Friend Plantation (Box 139)
      - Robinson (Box 139)
      - Pemiscot (Box 139)
      - Stanley (Box 139)
      - Rose (Box 140)
      - Halcomb (Box 140)
      - Mississippi
        - Sawyer's Landing (Box 141)
        - Richland (Box 141)
      - Middle Mississippi (Box 141)
      - St. Francis
        - Whitehall Place (Box 141)
        - Togo (Box 141)
        - Twist Place (Box 141)
        - Fuller Conner Place (Box 141)
        - Allcorn Place (Box 141)
        - Turkey Island (Box 141)
        - Cummings Place (Box 141)
        - Miller Place (Box 141)
        - M.W. Hazel Place (Box 141)
        - Marked Tree (Box 141)
        - R.C. Nichols Place (Box 141)
        - Hughes (Box 141)
        - G.C. Brown Place (Box 141)
        - Old Town Ridge (Box 141)
        - Bradley (Box 141)
        - Helena (Box 141)
        - G. Looney Place (Box 141)
        - Le Foe Place (Box 141)
        - L.W. Gosnell Place (Box 141)
        - P.H. Nodgrass Place (Box 141)
        - A.S. Catching Place (Box 141)
        - Higginbotham Place (Box 141)
        - Bassett (Box 141)
        - James Place (Box 141)
        - Joiner (Box 141)
        - White River (Box 141)
        - Chandler Landing (Box 141)
        - Mosier (Box 141)
        - Gulpha (Box 141)
      - Lower Mississippi
        - Haley Place (Box 142)
      - Belcher
        - Battle Place (Box 142)
        - McClure Place (Box 142)
        - Friday Place (Box 142)
        - Moore Place (Box 142)
        - Foster Place (Box 142)
        - Crenshaw Place (Box 142)
        - Lafayette County (Box 142)
        - Washington (Box 142)
        - Ozan 1, Flowers (Box 142)
        - Ozan 4, Eb. Brown (Box 142)
        - Ozan 5, Cole Place (Box 142)
        - Ozan 11, Goodlett (Box 142)
        - Jones Place (Box 142)
        - Boytt's Field (Box 142)
        - Keller Place (Box 142)
        - Kent (Box 142)
        - Wherry Landing (Box 142)
        - Tisdale Place (Box 142)
        - Emerson Place (Box 142)
        - Sumpter Place (Box 142)
        - Stanley Place (Box 142)
        - Gibson Place (Box 142)
        - Williamson Place (Box 142)
        - Mineral Springs (Box 143)
        - Hot Springs (Box 143)
        - Hot Springs 3, Ritter (Box 143)
        - Hot Springs 5, Robbins (Box 143)
        - Faulkner County (Box 143)
        - Conway County (Box 143)
        - Pope County (Box 143)
        - White County (Box 143)
      - Carden Bottum
        - Greer (Box 143)
        - Douglas (Box 143)
      - Upper Nodena (Box 143)
      - Middle Nodena (Box 143)
      - Nodena (Box 144)
      - Walnut Mound (Box 144)
      - Cross County (Box 145)
      - St. Francis County (Box 145)
      - Poinsett County (Box 145)
      - Mississippi County (Box 145)
      - Blytheville (Box 145)
      - Chickasawaba (Box 145)
      - Little Warren (Box 145)
      - Lee County (Box 145)
      - Jefferson County (Box 145)
      - Morgan Point (Box 145)
      - Lindey Landing (Box 145)
      - Rhodes Place (Box 145)
      - Davenport Collection (Box 145)
      - Buffalo Collection (Box 146)
      - Lilly Collection (Box 146)
    - Alabama
      - Tennessee Valley Sites
        - Deposit Landing, Ms14 (Box 146)
        - McKee Island, Ms32 (Box 146)
        - Cartright, MS 109, Ms 35 (Box 146)
        - Gunters Landing, Ms39 (Box 146)
        - Houston Site, Ms43 (Box 146)
        - Town Creek Site, Ms55 (Box 146)
        - Harris Site, Ms80 (Box 146)
        - Columbus City, Ms91 (Box 146)
        - Laws Site, Ms100 (Box 146)
        - Hall's Site, Ms107 (Box 146)
        - Stephenson, Ms111 (Box 146)
        - Pine Island, Ms121 (Box 146)
        - McDonald, Ms147 (Box 146)
        - Langston Site, Ja9a (Box 146)
        - Hardin Site, Ja27 (Box 146)
        - Sauty Site, Ja28 (Box 146)
        - Riley Site, Ja28a (Box 146)
        - Snodgrass Site, Ja101 (Box 147)
        - Sublet Site, Ja102 (Box 147)
        - Benson Site, Ja120 (Box 147)
        - Stearns Site, Ja155a (Box 147)
        - Crow Creek Island, Ja155 (Box 147)
        - Cox Site, Ja176 (Box 147)
        - Cox Site, Ja176a (Box 147)
        - Rudder Site, Ja180 (Box 147)
        - Rudder Site, Ja180a (Box 147)
        - Whitesburg Bridge, Ma10 (Box 147)
        - Huston, Lu86 (Box 147)
        - McKelvey Mound, Hn1 (Box 147)
        - Seven Mile Island, Lu21 (Box 147)
        - Koger's Island, Lu92 (Box 147)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 147)
        - Lon Robertson Place (Box 148)
        - Rhode's Place (Box 148)
        - Tu (Box 148)
        - Mad (Box 148)
        - Bessemer (Box 148)
        - Mason Island, Li36 (Box 148)
        - Flint Creek, Mg2 (Box 148)
        - Mulberry Creek, Ct27 (Box 148)
        - Ct8 (Box 148)
        - Cove Creek, Ct17 (Box 148)
        - Georgetown Mound, Ct34 (Box 148)
        - O'Neal, Lu61 (Box 148)
        - Meander Scar, Lu62 (Box 148)
      - Alabama Pottery Types
        - O'Neal Plain (Box 149)
        - Mulberry Creek Plain (Box 149)
        - McKelvey Plain (Box 149)
      - Alabama Cultures
        - Long Branch, Lu67 (Box 149)
        - Union Hollow, Lu72 (Box 149)
        - Mississippi (Box 149)
        - Middle Mississippi (Box 149)
        - Gordon-Fewkes (Box 149)
        - Moundville
          - WR (Box 149)
          - WP (Box 149)
          - SWM (Box 149)
          - SHE (Box 149)
          - SED (Box 149)
          - SD (Box 149)
          - NR (Box 149)
          - NN (Box 149)
          - NG (Box 149)
          - NED (Box 149)
          - NE (Box 149)
          - ND (Box 149)
          - NC (Box 149)
          - NB (Box 149)
          - MI (Box 149)
          - EI (Box 149)
          - EE (Box 149)
          - ED (Box 149)
          - Abercrombie-Fitzgerald (Box 149)
          - Ft. Walton (Box 149)
          - Bear Point (Box 149)
          - Simpson Island (Box 149)
          - Charlotte Thompson Place (Box 149)
          - Thirty Acre Field (Box 149)
          - Durand's Bend (Box 149)
          - Tulsa (Box 149)
          - Matthew's Landing (Box 149)
          - Little River (Box 149)
          - Weeden Island (Box 149)
          - Bashi Creek (Box 149)
          - Carney's Bluff (Box 149)
          - Payne's Woodyard (Box 149)
          - Kimbell's Field (Box 149)
          - Starke's Wharf (Box 149)
          - Clarke Co. (Box 149)
          - Ba80 (Box 149)
          - Coden, Mb1 (Box 149)
        - Guntersville (Box 150)
          - Colbert (Box 150)
        - Hopewellian
          - McQuorquodale, Ck25 (Box 150)
          - Hope Hull (Box 150)
          - Parkers Ferry (Box 150)
          - Huster, Ts2 (Box 150)
          - Northport, Ts3 (Box 150)
          - Blakely (Box 150)
          - Jackson (Box 150)
        - Copena
          - Fisher Site, Hn4 (Box 150)
          - Fisher Village, Hn4x1x2x3 (Box 150)
          - Boyd's Landing, Hn49 (Box 150)
          - Harris, La14 (Box 150)
          - Big Nance, La37 (Box 150)
          - Lamb's Ferry Cave, La40 (Box 150)
          - Georgetown Cave, Ct42 (Box 150)
          - Slaughter Place (Box 150)
          - Colbert Creek Site, Lu34 (Box 150)
          - Wright Mound No. 1, Lu63 (Box 150)
          - Wright Mound No. 2, Lu64 (Box 150)
          - Wright Village Site, Lu65 (Box 150)
          - Roden Mounds (Box 150)
          - Roden Site, Ms48 (Box 150)
          - Roden Site, Ms49 (Box 150)
          - Roden Site, Ms51 (Box 150)
          - Roden Site, Ms53 (Box 150)
          - Roden Site, Ms53a (Box 150)
          - Ross Site, Ms134 (Box 150)
          - Samuel's Site, Ms136 (Box 150)
          - Samuel's Site, Ms137 (Box 150)
          - Dispennett Cave, Ms142 (Box 150)
          - Hampton Cave, Ms145 (Box 150)
          - Hood, La13 (Box 150)
          - Hobb's Island, Ma1 (Box 150)
          - Hobb's Island, Ma3 (Box 150)
          - Hobb's Island, Ma4 (Box 150)
          - Hobb's Island, Ma5 (Box 151)
          - Flint River, Ma48 (Box 151)
          - Smithsonia, Lu5 (Box 151)
          - Perry, Lu25 (Box 151)
    - New England
      - Connecticut
        - Barnum Avenue (Box 152)
        - Muskrat Hill (Box 152)
        - Berkshire (Box 152)
        - Wojsicki (Box 152)
        - Nettleton (Box 152)
        - Fort Shantok (Box 152)
        - Windsor (Box 152)
        - Indian River (Box 152)
        - North Beach (Box 152)
        - Sebonac (Box 152)
        - South Woodstock (Box 152)
        - Clearview (Box 152)
        - Laurel Beach (Box 152)
        - Oronoque (Box 152)
        - Niantic (Box 152)
        - Smith Cove (Box 152)
        - Vine Valley (Box 152)
      - Maine
        - Red Paint (Box 152)
        - Alamoosook (Box 152)
        - Ellsworth (Box 152)
        - St. Georges (Box 152)
        - Kennebec (Box 152)
      - Massachusetts
        - Wapanucket (Box 152)
        - Clark's Pond (Box 152)
        - Foster's Cove, Eaton (Box 152)
        - Hofmann (Box 152)
        - Holyoke (Box 152)
        - Hornblower (Box 152)
        - Pringle (Box 152)
        - Squibnocket (Box 152)
      - Rhode Island
        - Potter Pond (Box 152)
        - Mill River Site (Box 152)
      - Vermont
        - Swanton (Box 152)
        - Orwell (Box 152)
      - New Hampshire (Box 152)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Shoop (Box 153)
      - Meadowcroft (Box 153)
      - Long (Box 153)
      - Wainwright (Box 153)
      - Safe Harbor (Box 153)
      - W.B. Strickler (Box 153)
      - Washingtonboro (Box 153)
      - Shenk's Ferry (Box 153)
      - McFate (Box 153)
      - Brock Mound and Village Site, Muncy (Box 153)
      - Erie (unknown and East 28th Street) (Box 153)
      - Br5 (Box 153)
      - Thurston Orchard, Br41 (Box 153)
      - Brennan Site, Br42 (Box 153)
      - Sick, B50 (Box 153)
      - Cass, B57 (Box 153)
      - Smith (Box 153)
      - Ellis Creek (Box 153)
      - Litchfield Station (Box 153)
      - Queen Ester's Flats, South End Milan Site (Box 153)
      - Queen Ester's Flats, Point (Box 153)
      - Azilum (Box 153)
      - Hufford Site (Box 153)
      - Naegal Site (Box 153)
      - Lyons Site (Box 153)
      - Woodland
        - Fuller's Hill (Box 153)
        - Montague (Box 153)
        - Hanna (Box 153)
        - Greene County (Box 153)
        - Bruckner (Box 153)
    - North Carolina
      - General (Box 154)
      - Leak (Box 154)
      - Peachtree (Box 154)
      - Birdtown (Box 154)
      - Sawnooke (Box 154)
      - Jasper Allan (Box 154)
      - Tuckasegee (Box 154)
      - Pisgah (Box 154)
      - Keyauwee, Rd1 (Box 154)
      - Wall, Or11 -- Occaneechi (Box 154)
      - Dv1, Saponi (Box 154)
      - Glenn, Rk1 -- Lower Sara (Box 154)
      - Gv1 (Box 154)
      - Plott-Smathers (Box 154)
      - Town Frutchey Creek (Box 154)
      - Hardaway (Box 154)
      - Puette (Box 154)
    - Virginia
      - Woodland
        - Clarksville (Box 154)
        - Gala (Box 154)
        - Clover Creek (Box 154)
        - Linville (Box 154)
        - The Cove (Box 154)
        - Bell Mounds (Box 154)
        - Haye's Creek Mound (Box 154)
        - Keyser Site (Box 154)
    - Maryland
      - Nassawango Ck. (Box 154)
      - Ferguson (Box 154)
      - Sharptown (Box 154)
      - Patuxent and Severn Rivers, Rock Creek (Box 154)
      - West River (Box 154)
    - Delaware (Box 154)
    - New Jersey
      - Masonville (Box 154)
      - Medford (Box 154)
      - Rancocas (Box 154)
      - Savich (Box 154)
    - West Virginia
      - St. Albans (Box 154)
      - Rohr Rockshelter (Box 154)
      - Clifton (Box 154)
      - Clover (Box 154)
      - Speidel Farm (Box 155)
      - Wells Farm (Box 155)
      - Half Moon Farm, Sites 29 and 30 (Box 155)
      - Wilkinson, Site 22 (Box 155)
      - Mont Hughes, Site 9 (Box 155)
      - Site 24 (Box 155)
      - Brown-Watson, Site 34 (Box 155)
      - Schuetz, Site 8 (Box 155)
      - Site 31 (Box 155)
      - Marmet, Site 1 (Box 155)
      - Site 21
      - Moundsville (Box 155)
      - Orchard (Box 155)
    - New York
      - New York Pottery Types (Box 155)
      - General (Box 155)
      - Hopewellian
        - Mound Intrusion (Box 155)
      - New York
        - Squawkie Hill (Box 155)
        - Geneseo Mound (Box 155)
      - Vine Valley (Box 155)
      - Middlesex
        - Palatine Bridge (Box 155)
        - Vine Valley (Box 155)
      - Point Peninsula
        - Point Peninsula (Box 155)
        - Northrop (Box 155)
        - Jack's Reef (Box 155)
        - Sea Breeze (Box 155)
        - Oberlander 2 (Box 155)
        - Fort Ticonderoga (Box 155)
        - Port Maitland (Box 155)
        - Fall Brook and West Rush (Box 155)
        - Vinette (Box 155)
        - Kipp Island (Box 155)
        - Rene Menard Bridge (Box 155)
        - Avon (Box 155)
      - Woodland (Box 155)
      - Northeastern
        - Archaic (Box 155)
      - Lamoka
        - Lamoka Lake (Box 155)
        - Scottsville (Box 155)
        - Geneva (Box 155)
      - Laurentian
        - Frontenac Island (Box 155)
      - Brewerton
        - Robinson (Box 155)
        - Oberlander 1 (Box 156)
        - Smoky Hollow (Box 156)
      - Vosberg
        - Vosburg (Box 156)
        - Manning and Round Lake (Box 156)
      - Vergennes (Box 156)
      - Orient (Box 156)
      - Coastal
        - Long Island (Box 156)
      - Early Focus (Box 156)
      - "Late" (Box 156)
      - Owasco
        - Oakfield (Box 156)
      - Castle Creek
        - Castle Creek (Box 156)
        - Bainbridge (Box 156)
      - Canandaigua
        - Canandaigua Site (Box 156)
        - Hilltop (Box 156)
        - Levanna (Box 156)
        - Second Algonkian (Box 156)
        - Third Algonkian (Box 156)
        - Railroad Bridge (Box 156)
      - Generalized Iroquois (Box 157)
      - Westfield (Box 157)
      - Integrated Iroquois (Box 157)
      - Esapus
        - Kingston (Box 157)
      - Mohawk
        - Jackson (Box 157)
        - Martin (Box 157)
        - Rice's Woods (Box 157)
        - Wagoner's Hollow (Box 157)
        - Ganada (Box 157)
        - Garoga (Box 157)
        - Clock (Box 157)
        - Cayadutta (Box 157)
        - Otstungo (Box 157)
        - Chance (Box 157)
        - Oak Hill (Box 157)
        - Goodyear Lake (Box 157)
        - Damascus (Box 157)
      - Oneida
        - Fort Plain (Box 157)
        - Buyer (Box 157)
        - Goff (Box 157)
        - Iseman (Box 157)
        - Diable (Box 157)
        - Cameron (Box 157)
        - Beecher (Box 157)
        - Thurston (Box 157)
        - Marshall (Box 157)
        - Quarry (Box 157)
        - Misc. Sites (Box 157)
      - Onondaga
        - Calkins (Box 157)
        - Parker's Pond (Box 157)
        - Jamesville I (Box 157)
        - Wallace (Box 157)
        - Durfee (Box 157)
        - Dry Hill (Box 157)
        - Indian Hill (Box 157)
        - Pompey Center (Box 157)
        - Misc. Sites (Box 157)
      - Cayuga
        - Woodley (Box 157)
        - Kings Fy. (Box 157)
        - Salmon Creek (Box 157)
        - Waterburg (Box 157)
        - Dansville Ft. (Box 157)
        - Richmond Mills (Box 157)
        - Le Roy (Box 157)
        - Myers Sta. (Box 157)
        - Genoa Ft. (Box 157)
        - Scipioville (Box 157)
      - Seneca
        - Canowangus (Box 157)
        - Dansville Flats (Box 157)
        - Dennis (Box 157)
        - Long Point (Box 157)
        - Factory Hollow (Box 157)
        - Dutch Hollow (Box 158)
        - So. Lima (Box 158)
        - Cornish (Box 158)
        - Warren (Box 158)
        - Steele (Box 158)
        - Silverheels (Box 158)
        - Marsh (Box 158)
        - Rochester Jct. (Box 158)
        - Snyder (Box 158)
        - Beal (Box 158)
        - Boughton Hill (Box 158)
        - Dann (Box 158)
        - Misc. Sites (Box 158)
      - Erie
        - Ripley (Box 158)
        - Orchard Park (Box 158)
      - Neutral